# PETER EVANS

**♀** 35 Kingfisher Road, Buckingham, MK18 7EX, UK

#### **PROFILE**

Recent MSci Physics graduate currently studying for an MSc in Applied Data Science, graduating December 2021.

Experienced in using Python as part of a complete data science life cycle - initially to collect, cleanse and analyse data before undertaking feature engineering and model building (regression, classification and clustering on both structured and text data).

Example projects available on portfolio website.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### University of Buckingham

2021 -

MSc in Applied Data Science, predicted Distinction.

# University of Bristol

2015 - 2019

MSci in Physics with First-Class Honours.

### Royal Latin School

2008 - 2015

AAB in Physics, Mathematics and Chemistry A Levels respectively.

7 A\*s, 3 As and 1 B achieved at GCSE level.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Digital Analytics Coordinator**

Oct 2021 -

University of Buckingham

- · Responsible for building insightful, dynamically updating dashboards using both Tableau and Google Data Studio in order to optimise return on investment of digital marketing activity.
- · The role has required a particular focus on regular expressions in order to filter user-inputted data.

#### English as a Foreign Language Teacher

Oct 2019 - Mar 2020

American Language Academy

- · Year abroad working as a teacher enabled me to develop many soft skills, especially communication and leadership.
- · Primarily worked with business executives to improve their English skills for the professional environment.

# Technical Intern - Cyber Insights GCHQ

Jul 2018 - Sep 2018

- · Studied various technologies of the cyber field at the organisation's annual summer school, covering topics such as secure coding, reverse engineering and pen testing.
- · Consisted of a variety of workshops to practise cyber skills for example, crashing a virtual machine with malware or using a weakness in an IoT device to break into its network.

Manager

Mar 2017 - Jun 2018

InHouse Media

· Co-managed a student-led video production company that created promotional videos for a variety of clients.

#### Various Hospitality Positions

2015 - 2020

Mutliple Agencies

· Temporary roles in order to be able to fund studies, which required working in very fast-paced environments.

#### **SKILLS & TECHNOLOGIES**

Tech Stack Python (NumPy, Pandas, scikit-learn, BeautifulSoup, Matplotlib, spaCy, NLTK, PySpark),

SQL, GitHub, Tableau, Google Data Studio, Google Analytics, Excel, Word, LaTeX.

Other Limited working proficiency level in Spanish. Full UK driving licence.